<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://Grideashuhan.github.io/</id>
    <title>Gridea</title>
    <updated>2020-10-31T05:53:29.656Z</updated>
    <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://Grideashuhan.github.io/"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://Grideashuhan.github.io/atom.xml"/>
    <subtitle>温故而知新</subtitle>
    <logo>https://Grideashuhan.github.io/images/avatar.png</logo>
    <icon>https://Grideashuhan.github.io/favicon.ico</icon>
    <rights>All rights reserved 2020, Gridea</rights>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[我的十七]]></title>
        <id>https://Grideashuhan.github.io/post/asgfw/</id>
        <link href="https://Grideashuhan.github.io/post/asgfw/">
        </link>
        <updated>2020-10-30T07:20:35.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>自由地去追寻自己的目标并不是任何事都可以随心所欲，为所欲为，真正自由地去追逐梦想的人懂得如何去安置自己不安的灵魂，而不是一味地任凭感觉。</p>
<p>十八岁之前做锦上添花者<br>
十八岁之后做雪中送炭人<br>
生而自由，爱而无畏</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My experience in villages]]></title>
        <id>https://Grideashuhan.github.io/post/warf/</id>
        <link href="https://Grideashuhan.github.io/post/warf/">
        </link>
        <updated>2020-10-30T07:20:24.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>看着一盆盆野草，我有时会想起我们这些从乡村移居到城市生活的人，尽管我们适应了盆里的生活，其实并未改变来自乡野的姿色，而所有的都市人，他们或他们的祖先，不都是来自乡野吗？只是有的人成了名花，忘记了自己的所在罢了。自然的本身是平等无二的，在乡野的山谷我们看见了自然的宏伟，在小小的花盆里，不也充满了生命的神奇吗？</p>
<p>Looking at the potted weeds, I sometimes think of those of us who have moved from the country to the city. Although we have adapted to the life in the pot, we have not changed the beauty of the countryside, and all the urbanites, or their ancestors, are from the countryside.It's just that some people become famous and forget where they are.Nature itself is equal, in the valley of the countryside we saw the grandeur of nature, in the small flowerpot, is not also filled with the magic of life?</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SOME THING I LEARNED IN CLIMATE&HEALTH CLASS/4]]></title>
        <id>https://Grideashuhan.github.io/post/sedfv/</id>
        <link href="https://Grideashuhan.github.io/post/sedfv/">
        </link>
        <updated>2020-10-29T07:58:29.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Nutrition<br>
How good is nutrition around the world?<br>
Feast and Famine<br>
A New Era for Nutrition<br>
Higher carbon dioxide concentrations substantially reduce nutrients such as protein, vitamin A, and folate, which are already in short supply for hundreds of millions of people worldwide.<br>
In the future, people having less and less access to some of wild foods.(carnivores, because of sustainable hunting).<br>
Green house gas emissions—sea temperature will rise----ocean acidification will occur----fish populations will move further and further toward the poles.<br>
People will have less and less access to seafood.<br>
Populations at risk<br>
Measuring bodyweight<br>
Body mass index=weight in kg/(height in m)^2<br>
Normal range: 18.5-24.9<br>
Underweight people are common in Asia and Africa<br>
Overweight people are more common across the rest of the world<br>
The health effects of being underweight</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ MY Costume designing/2]]></title>
        <id>https://Grideashuhan.github.io/post/srg/</id>
        <link href="https://Grideashuhan.github.io/post/srg/">
        </link>
        <updated>2020-10-29T07:58:20.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<figure data-type="image" tabindex="1"><img src="https://Grideashuhan.github.io//post-images/1589353586478.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></figure>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My experience in scientific research/1]]></title>
        <id>https://Grideashuhan.github.io/post/wef/</id>
        <link href="https://Grideashuhan.github.io/post/wef/">
        </link>
        <updated>2020-10-14T12:07:45.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Microalgae are getting more and more attention in the field of the method of carbon sink because of their many advantages, but this technique still has some limitations and can further develop in many aspects.</p>
<p>The first problem is about the selection and cultivation of microalgae. Chlorella is one of the typical examples. Almost all natural Chlorella’s specific growth rate and degree of inhibition are various with a single concentration of CO2. And none of those natural microalgae are perfect to be the resource for carbon sink. Thus, further developing gene technology is important for the world in the future, such as the cell fusion method, the breeding techniques for cross breeding, and the gene marksmanship. For example, transcription regulators were cloned from Pseudomonas bacteria and transferred to cyanobacteria, where NA+ tolerance increased from 2.5% to 4.5%. By using those methods, the excellent advantages of different microalgae can be integrated into the same special microalgae, thus not only perfecting the microalgae bank, but also improving the carbon sequestration efficiency and reducing side effects.</p>
<p>The second problem is the efficiency of the Photobioreactor. Nowadays, it is difficult to increase the photosynthetic efficiency in the dense microalgae and since the algae’s requirements on light and temperature are too high, reactors with efficient control over these environmental factors need to be developed. Among many reactors, the most promising one is an airlift reactor structure, which is a multi-phase flow reactor structure developed from a bubble reactor. When the air and CO2 are mixed, they first enter the gas distributor and then distribute into the reactor, thus forming uniform and small bubbles and increasing the gas acceptance area, which can effectively improve the mass transfer efficiency of CO2, algal liquid and gas-liquid. Compared with the biological storage of the racetrack pool reactor and the horizontal tubular reactor, that of the airlift reactor decreases by nearly 25 times.</p>
<p>The third problem is its energy efficiency calculation, the establishment of a sound system to achieve large-scale factory production. The development of the following three aspects is the key to achieve high efficiency CO2 fixation and large-scale industrialization of microalgae in the future: the surface area of photobioreactor, the gas-liquid mass transfer efficiency and the light source design. Different photobioreactors have different characteristics at present. Open bioreactors are called economical and suitable for large scale construction systems. The efficiency of co2 fixation in closed reactors is high. Combining different reactors’ advantages, the application of efficient carbon sequestration technology in large-scale microalgal light reactor is the future research direction. And improving the attachment structure makes the bubbles more compact and unified, and increasing the residence time of bubbles in algal liquid can improve the CO2 fixation efficiency of microalgae. Considering the future environmental, social and economic benefits, it would be more meaningful for universities to develop photobioreactors for solar energy collection devices.</p>
<p>In a nutshell, although CO2 fixation of microalgae has important social and environmental benefits, there are still many technical problems to be overcome, and the application scope of microalgae is becoming larger and wider. In the future, if we can solve the problems of high-quality microalgae cultivation, research and development of efficient photobioreactors, and energy efficiency calculation, and establish a perfect system to realize large-scale factory production, we may also provide a new, economical and effective carbon sequestration model for solving energy, health, environmental and other problems.</p>
<p>Reference:<br>
[1]浅谈国内外CCUS示范项目经验，段玉燕<br>
[2]https://worldpopulationreview.com/country-rankings/greenhouse-gas-emissions- by-country<br>
[3]https://www.nationalgeographic.com/environment/2019/07/major-us-cities-will-face-unprecedente-climates-2050/<br>
[4] https://www.sciencedirect.com/topics/earth-and-planetary-sciences/microalgae<br>
[5] https://www.thesprucepets.com/defining-micro-and-macro-algae-2924083<br>
[6] https://baike.baidu.com/item/%E5%BE%AE%E8%97%BB/6961484?fr=aladdin<br>
[7] Wastewater_treatment_for_carbon_capture_and_utilization.pdf<br>
[8]杨磊.碳捕捉与封存技术浅论[J].应用能源技术,2014(01):11-14.</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My photography works/3]]></title>
        <id>https://Grideashuhan.github.io/post/sdfzzc/</id>
        <link href="https://Grideashuhan.github.io/post/sdfzzc/">
        </link>
        <updated>2020-10-14T12:07:34.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<figure data-type="image" tabindex="1"><img src="https://Grideashuhan.github.io//post-images/1604046393201.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></figure>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SOME THING I LEARNED IN CLIMATE&HEALTH CLASS/3]]></title>
        <id>https://Grideashuhan.github.io/post/sdgf/</id>
        <link href="https://Grideashuhan.github.io/post/sdgf/">
        </link>
        <updated>2020-09-14T12:39:09.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Infection<br>
Introduction to Infectious Disease<br>
Infectious diseases have greatest impact on children, the elderly, and the pregnant women.<br>
Vector-borne Disease<br>
The Basics of Vector-borne Disease<br>
Rainfall can substantially influence risk of vector-borne disease<br>
rainfall is associated with dengue outbreaks. Rain creates pools of water that can be breeding habitat for juvenile mosquitos.<br>
droughts may also promote vector-borne disease outbreaks.<br>
Waterborne Disease<br>
warming temperatures and more intense precipitation may favor waterborne disease outbreaks.<br>
rainfall washes pathogens contained in animal and human excrement into sewer systems and eventually into local water bodies where water may be drawn from for drinking or crop irrigation. Warmer temperatures may promote growth of pathogens.<br>
Cities and Sewers<br>
Some cities have drain pipes that carry stormwater run-off and sewage together.<br>
the sewer systems have outfall pipes that drain into local waterbodies to prevent sewage backing up into peoples' homes and onto streets.<br>
Research on cities and regions in the United States with combined sewers may be more likely to have E. coli contaminated water  and higher rates of emergency room visits External link after extreme rainfall events.<br>
Even cities with combined sewer system have been able to substantially reduce discharges of untreated sewage through a variety of actions.<br>
Harmful Algal and Cyanobacteria Blooms<br>
Causes of Algal and Cyanobacterial Blooms<br>
they can also produce toxins that are dangerous to wildlife and swimmers.<br>
Warmer ocean temperatures and heavier precipitation, which increases the delivery of nutrients, can promote the growth of algae and cyanobacteria.<br>
One of the key ingredients for a harmful algal bloom is nitrogen.(nitrogen based fertilizer)<br>
This scenario occurs wherever agriculture and rivers co-exist<br>
Health Effects of Harmful Algal Blooms<br>
Algal and cyanobacterial toxins cause a range of illness in humans and wildlife<br>
Eg: headaches, vomiting, diarrhea, and numbness or tingling.<br>
Algal Bloom Trends<br>
ocean acidification may promote even more abundant and toxic algal blooms<br>
Overview of Malaria</p>
<p>Malaria's Impact<br>
mostly in lowland tropical areas<br>
Almost half of the Earth's population currently live in areas where malaria can be transmitted.<br>
The incidence of malaria has been declining in many parts of the world, especially in Africa.<br>
Linear or nonlinear relationship.<br>
In a linear relationship, increasing one item always increases or decreases another at the same rate.<br>
Increasing one factor may increase or decrease a connected factor, depending on the situation.<br>
nonlinear approaches are necessary to understand infectious diseases in a changing climate.(reason: ecological systems are complex and they involve lots of interactions, which often end up being nonlinear because they involve things like desity dependence, competition that have some optimum that might turn over over time).<br>
The mosquito life style.<br>
The reproduction of malarial parasites involves stages in mosquitoes and in humans<br>
the mosquitoes lay their eggs in water.<br>
The time the parasite spends developing in the mosquitois known as the extrinsic incubation period.<br>
Temperature<br>
Mosquitos and temperature<br>
Warmer temperatures accelerate development until temperatures are high enough to be lethal. Colder temperatures slow development until development stops because it's too cold.( they are cold-blooded and cannot survive when temperatures get too hot or too cold.)<br>
Warmer temperatures promote higher biting rates and faster parasite development.<br>
high temperatures also increase mosquito mortality.<br>
Development<br>
Temperature and Development<br>
the same amount of temperature variability does not affect all mosquito vectors equally.<br>
Altitude<br>
Temperature and Altitude<br>
climate warms, it may facilitate the spread of malaria to higher elevations, which were historically too cool for the disease to gain a foothold.<br>
Many cities in mountainous regions in the tropics were established at altitudes high enough to make them safe from mosquitoes and the diseases they carry.<br>
High temperature doesn’t mean the is not malaria transmission.<br>
Humidity declining, transmission declining.<br>
Precipitation<br>
Malaria and Precipitation<br>
The mosquitoes that transmit malaria prefer standing pools of water to breed in.<br>
Saturated ground might be prone to flooding whereas dry compact earth could be perfect for development of small pools.<br>
Too much rain can ruin the pool.<br>
The complexity of infectious disease<br>
The Interplay of Natural Systems<br>
using models can and will yield valuable insights that may inform decisions about how best to manage climate-related disease emergence.<br>
Human Intervention<br>
We can reduce our vulnerability to insect bites via insecticide and bed netting, reduce our vulnerability to infection through nutrition and medicine, and control how much we come in contact with others.<br>
vast areas of the world had wetlands drained , which deprived mosquitoes of habitat. For another, widespread use of insecticides and antimalarial medications, such as chloroquine and its derivatives, have curtailed the prevalence of the mosquito vectors and parasites.<br>
Aedes Mosquitoes<br>
Case study: Aedes mosquitoes<br>
these mosquitoes bred in natural pools of water, such as treeholes, but with urbanization, they have adapted to breeding in used tires and water containers.<br>
Their ability to thrive in cities raises concerns for increased disease spread with the growth of cities,<br>
The water and sanitation or trash services are two of the most important components for high desities.<br>
They seem to blossom in these dense urban environments.（lots of people）<br>
From Global to Local Disease Forecasts<br>
Steps Forward<br>
The problem about making local prediction is that in any local environment, there so many different variables that zre changing.<br>
Marrying climate forecasts with infectious disease models provides another complication when it comes to predicting what climate change will mean for infectious disease in the future.<br>
Multiple Solutions<br>
At local scale, climate might not be one of the major drivers of changes in transmission.<br>
See longer transmission seasons.</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UN Online internship experience/2]]></title>
        <id>https://Grideashuhan.github.io/post/dghb/</id>
        <link href="https://Grideashuhan.github.io/post/dghb/">
        </link>
        <updated>2020-09-14T12:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<figure data-type="image" tabindex="1"><img src="https://Grideashuhan.github.io//post-images/1604063776506.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></figure>
<p>In this class, Mr. Eric introduce us about the human face of climate change, a new dynamic from the amazon, the fire to wreak havoc in recent months flooding along the Yangtze river basin in China, to the melting of the Greenland ice sheet, July is the hottest July since records began in the northern hemisphere, and arctic sea ice reached a record low, especially in August 16, the United States of California and Nevada border Furnace Creek (Furnace Creek) region, the highest temperature of 54.4 ℃, is at least a century (perhaps) ever since one of the world's highest temperature.</p>
<p>Facing the climate change, countries attaches great importance to the Solution of Based on natural (Nature -based Solution), from America, costa rica, ecological protection to Rwanda in Africa, China's hills and green action, India's large-scale afforestation, xi President about to put an end to food waste in hundreds of millions of Chinese people's actions, such as construction waste in the whole society are proud of the shameful, saving the atmosphere of the instructions, in addition to the huge social benefits, also can produce huge greenhouse gas emission reduction benefits.</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is it wasteful for women to be housewives?]]></title>
        <id>https://Grideashuhan.github.io/post/sgdetg/</id>
        <link href="https://Grideashuhan.github.io/post/sgdetg/">
        </link>
        <updated>2020-09-14T12:38:49.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Today, I saw a hot search on whether it is  wasteful for women to be a housewife. Many people in the comment section think it is a waste, because what housewives want to do is not in line with the knowledge they receive, then they are wasting the value they should give play to.</p>
<p>In my opinion, I strongly oppose this argument. The meaning of education is to develop one's way of thinking rather than skills. Any choice of women and the consequences of their choice are determined by their thoughts, and women should not be labelled as &quot;wasteful&quot; because they choose anything.</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[保护环境的目的]]></title>
        <id>https://Grideashuhan.github.io/post/hi/</id>
        <link href="https://Grideashuhan.github.io/post/hi/">
        </link>
        <updated>2020-09-13T05:40:08.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>目前观点仍停留在“为人类后代服务”的自私出发点上。我认为，如果保护生命的动机不是出于对其存在的敬畏与尊重，那么一切的行动都是自私的。孩子们的课本上写着“保护地球就是保护人类自己”——典型的利己思想，单从这一点看，我们离动物福利事业的达成还有一定的距离。</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
</feed>